Allen Varley Astin Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Professional Activities, 1928-1984 (Box 28-61)
  - State Department, Bureau of International Scientific and Technological Affairs
    - United States-Japan Committee on Scientific Cooperation (Box 53)
      - Member, 1972-1976, (5 folders) (Box 56)
  - Transportation Department, National Motor Vehicle Safety Advisory Council
    - Committees
      - Crash survivability, 1970-1971
      - General, 1970-1972
      - Research, 1968-1972
    - Correspondence, 1969-1972, (3 folders) (Box 57)
    - First International Congress on Automotive Safety, San Francisco, Calif., 1972, (2 folders)
    - Membership lists, 1967-1971
    - Memoranda, 1971-1972, undated, (3 folders) (Box 58)
    - Minutes, 1970-1972
    - Miscellany, 1970-1973, undated, (2 folders)
    - Partnership in Safety Conferences, 1971 (Box 59)
      - Key Biscayne, Fla.
      - San Francisco, Calif.
    - Reports, 1969-1973, (3 folders)
    - Second International Technical Conference, Stuttgart, Germany, 1971
    - Tires, 1969-1971 (Box 60)
  - Underwriters' Laboratories, Chicago, Ill.
    - Board of Trustees, 1969-1976, (5 folders)
    - Printed matter, 1974-1975
  - United States Air Force Scientific Advisory Board, 1949-1953
  - United States Metric Board, 1975-1978 (Box 61)
- Miscellany, 1934-1984 (Box 61-66)
  Commerce Department file and family and personal papers, including correspondence, memoranda, photographs, press releases, appointment calendars, reports, financial records, minutes, and programs.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject or type of material.
  - Commerce Department, acting assistant secretary for science and technology, 1967-1969 (Box 61)
  - Family and personal papers, 1934-1983, undated
    - Appointment calendars
      - 1951-1959, (2 folders)
      - 1960-1981, (6 folders) (Box 62)
    - Correspondence, 1947-1983, undated, (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - Gardening
      - Jackson-Perkins Rose Testing Panel, 1960-1982, undated
      - Miscellany, 1975-1982, undated
    - Income tax records, 1934-1964, (2 folders)
    - Papers pertaining to other family members (Box 64)
      - Astin, Alexander, 1956-1970, undated, (2 folders)
      - Astin, John, 1935, 1950-1977, undated
      - Miscellany, 1943-1975, undated
    - Philatelic interests, 1957-1965, undated
    - Social activities
      - Awards ceremonies, banquets, celebrations, 1950-1954, (2 folders)
      - Cosmos Club, Washington, D.C.
        - Board of Management
          - Correspondence, 1962-1966
          - Financial statements, 1964-1966 (Box 65)
          - Minutes, 1962-1984, (4 folders)
          - Reports, 1962-1966
        - Briggs, Lyman James, tribute, 1936-1979, undated, (5 folders) (Box 66)
        - Haddon, William, membership nomination, 1974-1979, undated
        - Miscellaneous, 1950-1969, undated
      - Gridiron Club, Washington, D.C., program, 1953
      - Miscellaneous, 1935, 1951-1953